<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Web3 - Category - MrUnomi</title>
    <link>https://rohitgoswami.in/categories/web3/</link>
    <description>Web3 - Category | MrUnomi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 00:00:00 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rohitgoswami.in/categories/web3/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
  <title>zkFetch: Secure Data Fetching with Zero-Knowledge Proofs</title>
  <link>https://rohitgoswami.in/posts/zkfetch/</link>
  <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>https://rohitgoswami.in/posts/zkfetch/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[IntroductionzkFetch is a library that extends the functionality of a standard HTTP fetch operation by adding a zero-knowledge proof component. The main goal is to allow users to fetch data from remote resources and generate a cryptographic proof of the fetch operation and its result, without revealing sensitive information like API keys or private headers.
Core ConceptsZero-Knowledge Proofs (ZKP)At the heart of zkFetch is the concept of zero-knowledge proofs.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Demystifying Sui&#39;s Mysticeti</title>
  <link>https://rohitgoswami.in/posts/mysticeti/</link>
  <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>https://rohitgoswami.in/posts/mysticeti/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[Mysticeti: The Breakthrough Consensus Protocol Now on Sui MainnetRecently Sui Foundation has launched Mysticeti on Mainnet, the groundbreaking consensus protocol that has reduced consensus time on Testnet by a staggering 80 percent!
Mysticeti achieves the fastest overarching latency, reaching consensus on Testnet in just 390ms with 640ms settlement finality. This is an 80% reduction from the previous Narwhal-Bullshark protocol
The Sui blockchain, already known for its impressive transaction speeds, is set to get even faster with the introduction of a new Byzantine consensus protocol called Mysticeti.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
